Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Unblocked by the波に乗ろう
力合わせて
時めく方へ急ごう
始まりの合図
今こそ船出の時
光を上げたら
7色の風を切り 冒険の海へ
傷だらけの旅だけど 大事なものがそこにある
銀紙ならいつだって 僕が守るから
大丈夫さ 前に進もう 舞い合おういつも胸に
嵐が来たら肩組んで その先の光を見よう
夢の欠片集まれば 明日に向かう地図になる
だから同じ旗の下 願いをつかまえようよ
僕らはひとつ脇
あなたのアリア子が先に使ってはなりそれだか
大丈夫
It appears the fire is beginning to spread.
Leopard, human, whatever the hell you are, you're not going to lay one finger on Iceberg, you hear me?
No, he's a carnivore zoan type. They're the most brutal of them all.
Indeed. Logia types, zoan types, paramethia types. Each one extremely powerful in their own unique way.
The ability to enhance one's own personal strength happens to be the specialty of the zoan type.
In other words, the more we train, the stronger we get.
Which makes the zoan type the most lethal when it comes to attacks at close range.
Shut the hell up!
Nobody here gives a damn about what monster can do what.
Just as well, we're running out of time.
Before the flames engulf this place, we need to make sure that all of you are properly disposed of.
Iceberg!
Go! Move it!
Luchi, the workmen are making their way up the stairs.
Don't worry. They'll never make it this far.
Tempest kick!
Come back! The ceiling's collapsing!
Nummy!
Chopper!
What are you doing?
No matter what, I'm getting you out of here.
There's no way your wounds are far too...
I'm afraid we can't let you do that.
And I'm afraid...
You're gonna have to!
Step aside!
Get out of my way!
Damn you!
Why did it have to be you guys?
No...
I can't believe you!
How could you do this?
You tricked me!
I thought you were my friends!
Then you were mistaken.
Talking pigeon jerk!
Luffy, what are you?
Finger pistol.
Luffy!
No!
Have a nice flight!
Luffy!
Damn you!
Iron body!
Thuro!
That's right!
Now it's your turn!
Now it's your turn.
Oh...
I'm here!
You got to try!
It's time to try!
Now it's your turn!
You got to try!
Granny! Granny! There's a huge fire!
It's Galilaw's main office. Such a terrible thing to do.
What do you mean, Granny? Did someone start the fire on purpose?
Well, I can't really say for sure.
But usually, when I get a bad feeling, it turns out to be right.
I sure hope that Iceberg is doing okay.
Seriously, all this is happening over that thing. It shouldn't even exist.
The testimony of a pirate won't hold up as evidence. This case will remain a mystery.
Iceberg, no matter how great of a shipbuilding engineer you are, no matter how great a mayor,
a mere individual citizen shouldn't oppose the world government.
Let's go. We need to find Tom's other apprentice, Frankie.
Or, rather, Cuddy Flam and take those blueprints away from him.
Outro Music
We'll be right back.
I'm sure he's here somewhere.
Hey, wait.
That woman's one of the straw hats.
I'm sure of it.
Did she jump out from one of the windows?
She probably got trapped by the fire
and didn't have any other choice in the matter.
Well, what should we do with her?
These damn pirates have done a terrible thing here.
Let's make her tell us where the rest of her crew is.
We'll hunt them down and turn them over to the Navy.
You're sure of it.
You saw Frankie wandering into your bar earlier.
Yeah, I spoke with him.
But he took off to go look for Straw Hat.
I see.
Seems like he doesn't stay in one place for very long.
Wow.
Some people just have the worst sense of timing.
Look, there.
Listen up, Straw Hat!
We've got Long Nose!
That's right!
We totally have him!
If you don't want him to sing in the key of C!
You idiot!
How many times do I have to tell you
it's if you don't want him to sink into the sea!
Break some iced tea!
The sea!
Are you deaf?
What kind of threat is that?
It doesn't make any sense!
Whatever!
All that matters is getting a message to Straw Hat!
Giving him that stupid message won't do any good!
And bro Frankie will end up kicking your butt!
If you don't want him sunk to the bottom of the sea,
go to the warehouse under the bridge
with the guards breaking!
Like that!
If he gets a message and he does come,
bro's gonna beat the living crap out of him!
Who did you say is waiting for whom?
And where is this certain someone waiting?
Who the hell are you?
We're kind of busy right now!
Get lost!
If you want to live,
you'll answer my question in the next three seconds.
Huh?
Is that some kind of joke, you nutjob?
Do you even have the slightest clue
as to what family we're a part of?
What did you mean by the warehouse under the bridge?
Is that the place where Frankie is?
Whatever business you have with Frankie,
he's gonna have to go through us first!
Right, guys?
Yeah!
Ah!
I think that you left the friends you travel
you with all the way from the east blue for your ship!
Why in the world are the three of you crying about it?
What?
We're not crying, you idiot!
I was just thinking about everything you've been through
to protect that ship all alone,
and it touched my heart!
We're not crying!
None of us are crying!
What the heck is wrong with these nitwits?
Ah!
Anyway, you get the gist of it, right?
We're no longer friends!
The straw hats are part of my past now!
It's so sad!
It's so sad that I'll have to sing about it!
This song is called Severed Friendship, North Wind Child!
Yeah!
Sing it, bro!
Hey!
Are you making fun of me?
Oh, is the tea ready yet?
I'm dying of thirst over here!
Almost!
We'll bring it over in just a moment!
Thanks!
Ow!
That crying wore me out!
Not that I really cried!
Uh-uh!
Here you go, bro!
Now be careful!
It's really hot!
Uh-uh!
Ah, thank you so much!
Okay, I understand what's what, brother!
Whoa!
She just got through telling you that!
Calm down!
Sorry about that, bro!
You okay?
Why don't you take a break and have some tea as well?
Uh-uh!
I can't blame you.
You must be holding quite the grudge against us.
You know, since we stole your 200 million berries and all.
Especially because it led to such a big fight with your captain.
Whatever.
What happens, happens.
No sense holding a grudge about it.
Taking the high road.
Oh, manly.
About that money.
I spent all of it!
I'm gonna knock you flat.
Now, now.
Don't get so worked up.
Especially after you showed me how dignified and forgiving you are.
Come on, brother.
Can't we just let bygones be bygones?
I mean, I haven't flipped out on you for destroying my home and demolition factory, have I?
And on top of that, you guys annihilated my subordinates.
You bastards!
How dare you all kill you!
Easy, bro!
You gotta control that anger!
Yep, a lot has happened these past few days.
But I do think we're better off putting it all behind us.
So what do you say we just put the axe in the ground and call it a day?
I think you mean Barry the Hatchet.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure it's Barry the Hatchet, bro.
Yeah, what they said.
So...
You could do it.
So what do you say?
Yeah.
Someone else do this.
They're gonna go into this video.
夢見た僕らは間違いじゃないと信じて 荒く埋れる海原を渡って行ける
誰よりも勇敢で 思いやりもあるけれど
もしも君がこの船を降りて 違う世界にいたとしても
最後にはきっと笑えるよ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
I'm gonna be king of the pirates